Prepare for the next level.
xXx: State of the Union is a action, adventure,
crime film directed by Lee Tamahori.
Darius Stone's criminal record and extreme sports obsession make him
the perfect candidate to be the newest XXX agent.
He must save the U.S.
government from a deadly conspiracy led by five-star
general and Secretary of Defense George Deckert.
Darius Stone / xXx, played by Ice Cube.
Agent Augustus Gibbons, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Gen. George Octavius Deckert, played by Willem Dafoe.
Agent Kyle Steele, played by Scott Speedman.
President James Sandford, played by Peter Strauss.
Zeke, played by Xzibit.
XXX (stylized as xXx and pronounced Triple X) is an American
action spy film series created by Rich Wilkes.
It consists of three full-length feature films: XXX (2002), XXX: State of the Union (2005) and XXX:
Return of Xander Cage (2017), and a short film: The Final Chapter: The Death of Xander Cage.
The series has grossed $694 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of helicopter, usa president,
washington dc, usa, general, coup d'etat.
The tone is intense.